http://www.pacificdragons.com.au/privacy-policy

Pacific Dragons Privacy Policy – Pacific Dragons
Try Paddling About Us Our ClubAbout Dragon BoatingAbout Outrigger CanoeingAbout Single Craft PaddlingMeet our CanoesSponsorship and MediaOur Latest Major ResultsCommunity SupportLinksNew Member Info News Contact
Members HomePacific Dragons Privacy PolicyPacific Dragons Privacy PolicyWho we areOur website address is: https://www.pacificdragons.com.au.What personal data we collect and why we collect itCommentsWhen visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.MediaIf you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.Contact formsWe may collect information about you for 2 reasons: firstly, to process your order and second, to response to any queries which you may have.We will not e-mail you in the future unless you have given us your consent.We will give you the chance to refuse any marketing email from us in the future.The type of information we may collect about you includes:Your nameEmail addressPhone NumberIP AddressThe information we hold will be accurate and up to date. You can check the information that we hold about you by emailing us. If you find any inaccuracies we will delete or correct it promptly.The personal information which we hold will be held securely in accordance with our internal security policy and the law.We may use technology to track the patterns of behaviour of visitors to our site. This can include using a “cookie” which would be stored on your browser. You can usually modify your browser to prevent this happening. The information collected in this way can be used to identify you unless you modify your browser settings.CookiesIf you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.If you visit our login page, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. Logging out of your account will delete the cookies – therefore you will have to log in again.If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.Google MapsGoogle services is used to generate maps and provide autocompletion when searching for events by location, which may collect data via your browser in accordance to Google’s privacy policy.We collect and store information you submit to us when making a booking, for the purpose of reserving your requested spaces at our event and maintaining a record of attendance.Cookies are used to temporarily store information about a booking in progress as well as any error/confirmation messages whilst submitting or managing your events and locations.Embedded content from other websitesArticles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.Who we share your data withHow long we retain your dataIf you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognise and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.For users that register on our website, we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.What rights you have over your dataIf you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.Where we send your dataVisitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.Additional informationFor registered users, we store your Profile Data (email address, phone number and gender) in order to contact you, and to sort paddlers by gender.For registered users, coaches (for coaching purposes) may privately store information about you that you can request to see at any time.The website also records your attendance to events, in order to provide coaches with information in team selection. You can find this in your Profile Data page under History.Membership DataMembership data is not stored on this website. For data protection purposes, we store this information separately in a protected Google Document, that the Webmaster, Registra and Coaches have access to. You may request to see your information, at any time.How we protect your dataYour personal information stored on this site is encrypted. We have tried to mitigate risks by storing the least amount of data about you, in order for the club to function.This site is protected via the Secured Sockets Layer protocol ( SSL ) to encrypt communication between and your browser and the server. Your password is encrypted and is unrecoverable. We suggest that you don’t share passwords among other websites. We limit the amount of personal information stored on Registered Users, and have a virus scanner/malware detection software in place.What data breach procedures we have in placeIf this website is compromised, we will contact you and request that you change your password. We also provide clarification on what we think has happened, and how to prevent it from happening again.If you would like to know further any information please .Where we train
Dragon Boating: 1 Bank St. PyrmontOutrigger Canoe: Glebe High School, on the Blackwattle Bay Walk near Bridge St. GlebeSingle Craft: 62A Willoughby St, KirribilliWhen we trainWe have flexible training times to suit anybody.Mon: Dragon Boat – 6:40pmTue: Outrigger – 6:25pmWed: Dragon Boat – 6:40pmThu: Outrigger – 5:30am and 6:45pmFri: Single Craft – 5:30amSat: Dragon Boat –  8:10amSun: Outrigger – 7:30amContact UsHave any questions about our club, dragon boating, outrigging or training? Please get in touch! Contact Us
Privacy Policy | Terms and Conditions
